ANDERA SINGGIH PRATAMA

CREATIVE DESIGNER | MULTIMEDIA SPECIALIST | VISUAL COMMUNICATION

Address Banyumas

Phone +62 812 2950 9087

E-mail anderasinggih1@gmail.com

Creative designer proficient in Adobe Photoshop, After Effects, Premiere, and Illustrator. Strong skill set with fast learning ability, hardworking nature, and disciplined approach. Capable of excelling independently or as part of a team. Strong public speaking and effective communication skills. Dedication and expertise will be a valuable asset to this company.

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

· Instagram: @anderasinggih

· LinkedIn: Andera Singgih Pratama

Skills

Advanced Microsoft Office Skills

Experience with Adobe Applications

Visual Editing Expertise

Visual Editing Expertise

Work history

2020-03 - Current

Freelance Videographer & Editor

Freelance, Purwokerto

- Delivered polished videos on time by efficiently managing post-production tasks such as color grading, sound mixing, and visual effects creation.
- Collaborated with other production team members for successful completion of projects.
- Filmed live events and promotional videos, capturing memorable moments for a wide array of clientele.

2022-05 - 2022-08

Content Creator & Event Planner

HAF Management, Purwokerto

Applied current editing and photography tools to tell great stories.

2020-09 - 2021-03

Video Editor & Broadcaster

ISHPOT, Purwokerto

 Combined text, video and other composited elements onscreen to create logical, coherent layouts.

Education

2010-01 - 2016-01

Elementary School

SDN LEDUG - Banyumas, Indonesia

2016-01 - 2019-01

Junior High School

SMPN 6 PURWOKERTO - Purwokerto, Indonesia

2001-04 - 2022-01

Vocational High School Diploma: Software Engineering

TELKOM VACATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL PURWOKERTO - Purwokerto, Indonesia

2022-01 undefined

Bachelor of Computer Science: Software Engineering

TELKOM UNIVERSITY PURWOKERTO - Purwokerto, Indonesia

Personal Traits

Creative & Detail-Oriented

Able to think creatively and pay close attention to details in every design.

Fast Learner

Quickly adapts to new technologies and design trends.

Hardworking & Disciplined

Works with high dedication and excellent time management.

Team & Independent Worker

Capable of collaborating in a team or working independently.

Languages

Indonesian: Native language

English